{
    "id": "73168543156447c5b4eff4da3ac83470",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The patient ................................. yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "die",
                "died",
                "has died"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I .......................... the parcel yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "received",
                "have received",
                "had received",
                "was receiving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The sun ............................ when we started our journey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shone",
                "was shining",
                "had shone",
                "is shining"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw him ......................... the boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "beating",
                "to beat"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Yesterday I ————— a new laptop as my old one ————- quite slow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was buying, has become",
                "bought, had become",
                "had bought, became",
                "have bought, have become"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He thanked me for what I —————",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "have done",
                "had done",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ——————– on this project for two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am working",
                "was working",
                "have been working"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They —————- an apartment in Bangalore three years ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bought",
                "have bought",
                "had bought"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I usually —————– coffee in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drink",
                "am drinking",
                "will drink",
                "would drink"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Ever since I ————– my country in 2007, I ————— living in Canada.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left, have been",
                "have left, had been",
                "had left, have been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}